{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Bukowski",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Rhineland-Palatinate",
    "human_readable": "Charles Bukowski was born in Rhineland-Palatinate.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8945730328559875,
            "question": "Did Charles Bukowski live his whole life in Rhineland-Palatinate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8471475839614868,
            "question": "Where was Charles Bukowski born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7259310483932495,
            "question": "What other famous people were born in Rhineland-Palatinate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4603937566280365,
            "question": "What is Charles Bukowski known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4133555591106415,
            "question": "Which region in Germany is Rhineland-Palatinate located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23764106631278992,
            "question": "Was Charles Bukowski a novelist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1676902323961258,
            "question": "How did Charles Bukowski's life experiences influence his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16417711973190308,
            "question": "What type of writing style did Charles Bukowski use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1266663670539856,
            "question": "What were some of the major themes explored in Charles Bukowski's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12498734891414642,
            "question": "Are there any museums or literary centers dedicated to Charles Bukowski?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Bukowski was born in Rhineland-Palatinate.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4051_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the major themes explored in Charles Bukowski's writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4051_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of writing style did Charles Bukowski use?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4051_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Charles Bukowski's life experiences influence his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4051_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4051_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the answer to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while several documents mention Charles Bukowski's birthplace, none of them specify Rhineland-Palatinate specifically. Document 21 does mention \"Rhineland-Palatinate\" as part of his birth location, but it is mentioned in the context of also specifying Andernach and Weimar Germany."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Charles Bukowski's birthplace, stating that he was born in Andernach, Germany. Andernach is located in the state of Rhineland-Palatinate, which supports the statement that Charles Bukowski was born in Rhineland-Palatinate."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "He was born in Andernach, Germany which is not located in Rhineland-Palatinate.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}